A lot of evidence shows
that your father,
after stealing key information from the Ling Group,
while trying to escape,
unfortunately died in an accident.
Impossible.
My father wouldn't steal.
My father was murdered.
He is innocent.
I've told you so many times,
we can't take this case.
The evidence is conclusive.
There's really nothing we can do.
Please go back.
Attorney Guan,
I just want to save my dad.
There's really nothing I can do.
Lawyer Guan.
Please find someone else.
Ever since my father left me forever,
in my life,
I've been all alone.
I started studying law hard
and got my lawyer's license.
Just to step into this company
and avenge my father.
Your father's soul could have ascended to heaven immediately
to enjoy the peace of paradise.
But because he was worried about you,
he hid in the necklace and guarded you for five years.
Ghosts cannot stay in the mortal realm for long.
Otherwise, their souls will scatter.
He had reached his limit.
Are you saying my dad was in this necklace,
protecting me all this time?
Is he still there now?
Can I see him?
He has already reincarnated.
Thank you.
Don't forget your promise to me.
I won't forget.
You can't even manage a streamer.
I really don't know why I've raised you all these years.
I'm sorry, Father. I will definitely...
You have no right to call me Father.
No matter what method you use,
take care of it as soon as possible.
If the higher-ups behind me
are implicated,
you will bear the responsibility yourself.
If something really goes wrong,
you will have nothing to do with the Ling family.
Okay.
I really should have
told you to get lost with that crazy woman back then.
Can you only go back to this day?
Then the only way for us to come back
is through that?
Can't there be another way?
Why?
Whatever method was used the first time,
the same must be used from then on.
Then why did you have to kiss me the first time?
Lady.
You were drowning.
I was giving you oxygen.
I had no other choice.
You had no...
From now on, without my permission,
you are not allowed to use your powers.
Fine. As you wish.
Also, without my permission,
you are not allowed to enter my house.
I have nowhere else to live but your house.
What do you mean you can only live in my house?
I'm a single woman.
How is it appropriate for you to live here?
First.
My only mission is to protect you
and keep you from any danger.
Second.
I'm not interested in you.
So rest assured,
I will absolutely not do anything out of line.
Once your problem is solved,
I will leave.
Then let's make three rules.
First.
Without my permission,
you are not allowed to step into my room.
Second.
If you want to use anything in the house,
you must get my consent.
Third.
I haven't thought of the third one yet.
I'll tell you when I do.
Do you have a problem with that?
Never mind.
As you wish.
Nice working with you.
Since your powers are so strong,
why don't you just help me get rid of that jerk?
My powers cannot be used to harm humans.
Why?
Rules.
What do you mean by this?
What, do you have a problem?
You...
Morning, Lawyer Gu.
Morning.
Don't move.
Remember to come find me after you finish your onboarding.
Got it?
Where are you going?
Hold it steady.
Human heart.
If the company has any new evidence or witnesses,
just send them directly to my phone.
I'm leaving now.
Okay, I'll check.
This will be your new workstation from now on.
Okay.
Quick, now.
You only have two minutes.
Hurry back.
Got it.
Xingcan.
What's the matter?
Mr. Ling.
I just came to tell you
that I have all the materials ready,
and I'm going to pick up the witness now.
If there's nothing else, I'll get going.
That scared me to death.
I was almost exposed.
What's wrong?
You...
Why are you burning up?
You're as red as a crayfish.
Chenyao, wake up.
Chenyao.
Chenyao, don't scare me.
You look thin, but you're really heavy.